Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
I’m the one, I’m your idol
꾸준한 네 좋아요
너는 마치 loyal fan
훔쳐봐 with fan account
나는 원해 솔직함
날 가두지 마 보석함
Prada보다 비싼 대체불가 나인데
번잡한 옆 동네 넌 왜 거길 또 헤매
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
Who? Who?
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
It’s Me
Me, Me!
Hey, just say I’m your fave!
I yelled “너, hilarious!”
Oh my my my my
수수방관 like tortilla
Why? Why? Why? Why?
This 풋사랑 ain’t no joke
It can’t can’t can’t can’t
답답넙치!
Post me on your gram
Sphere 전광판엔 커플 이니셜 레터링
올려 우리 학교 대자보에 headline
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
Who? Who?
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
It’s Me
Me
Me, Me!
It’s Me
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
It’s Me
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
It’s Me
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!
It’s Me
Who’s your bias?
I’m your bias!